Guide to the Public Art Fund Archive MSS.270
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VI: Public Art Fund - Project Files
  - Subseries VI.A: Exhibitions and Projects (1977 - 2009), 1972-2009
    - Casebere, James, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Heap-of-Birds, Edgar, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Hewat, Christopher, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Group Material - "Inserts" - 1 of 2, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Group Material - "Inserts" - 2 of 2, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Kramer, Margia, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Kruger, Barbara, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Lawson, Thomas, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Min, Yong Soon, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Nonas, Richard, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Schafer, David, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Wilson, Fred, 1988 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Dwyer, Nancy, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Gaskin, Franco - "Franco the Great", 1989 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - General Idea - 1 of 3, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - General Idea - 2 of 3, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - General Idea - 3 of 3, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Gianakos, Steve, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Gonzalez-Torres, Felix - 1 of 2, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Gonzalez-Torres, Felix - 2 of 2, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Greengold, Jane, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Holzer, Jenny, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Katz, Joel - 1 of 3, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Katz, Joel - 2 of 3, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Katz, Joel - 3 of 3, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Kearns, Jerry, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Ladda, Justen, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Lemieux, Annette, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Rivera, Sophie, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Rollins, Tim + K.O.S. - 1 of 2, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Rollins, Tim + K.O.S. - 2 of 2, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Subway posters - General, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Van Dalen, Anton - 1 of 2, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - Van Dalen, Anton - 2 of 2, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - Winokur, Neil, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - Bursztyn, Dina, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - Cowin, Eileen, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - Fulbrecht, William - "Seeds", 1990 (Box 42, Folder 27)
    - Fulbrecht, William - "Bill of Rights", 1990 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Goulet, Michel, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Horsfield, Kate & Klonarides, "Carol Anne - Video Drive-in"/Central Park, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Menard, Andrew, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Meredith, Ann, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Michelson, Alan, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Muntadas, Antonio - 1 of 2, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Muntadas, Antonio - 2 of 2, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Nordman, Maria, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Shapiro, Joel, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Wong, Martin, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Cole, Jeffrey and Schafer, David, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Dill, Terry Lee, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Edwards, Melvin, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Gran Fury, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Guerrilla Girls, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Kroke, Pit, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Kruger, Barbara, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - Ressler, Robert, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Aiha, Martti, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - Allen, Jules, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Deon, Richard - 1 of 2, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Deon, Richard - 2 of 2, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Hauft, Amy - 1 of 2, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Hauft, Amy - 2 of 2, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Lee, Bing and Garson Yu, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Moore, Jesse, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Sonfist, Alan, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - "Trans Voices" - General - 1 of 2, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - "Trans Voices" - General - 2 of 2, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - "Trans Voices" - Declined, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - "Trans Voices" - Blain, Dominique, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - "Trans Voices" - Boltanski, Christian, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - "Trans Voices" - Cazal, Philippe, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - "Trans Voices" - Ennadre, Touhami, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - "Trans Voices" - Gerz, Jochen, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - "Trans Voices" - Jaar, Alfredo, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - "Trans Voices" - Lafontaine, Marie-jo, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - "Trans Voices" - Messager, Annette, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - "Trans Voices" - Simmons, Laurie, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - "Trans Voices" - Simpson, Lorna, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - "Trans Voices" - Teraoka, Masami, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - "Trans Voices: Questions for a New Order", 1992 (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - Botero, Fernando - 1 of 3, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - Botero, Fernando - 2 of 3, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - Botero, Fernando - 3 of 3, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 26)
    - Bunkley, Brit, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 27)
    - di Suvero, Mark, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Lacy, Suzanne - 1 of 2, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Lacy, Suzanne - 2 of 2, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Pepper, Beverly - 1 of 2, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Pepper, Beverly - 2 of 2, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Shearer, Rhonda Ronald - 1 of 2, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Shearer, Rhonda Ronald - 2 of 2, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - "Urban Paradise" - 1 of 5, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - "Urban Paradise" - 2 of 5, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - "Urban Paradise" - 3 of 5, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - "Urban Paradise" - 4 of 5, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - "Urban Paradise" - 5 of 5, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Boyer, Gilbert, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Flanagan, Barry, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Jones, Kristin and Andrew Ginzel, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Jordan, Lorna, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Ladda, Justen, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Mitchell, Tyrone, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Saar, Alison and Betye, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Shea, Judith, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Simmons, Gary, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Steinbach, Haim, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Strang, Gary; Roche, Michael; and Hewitt, Robert - "Urban Paradise", 1994 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Webster, Meg, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Acconci, Vito (1 of 2), 1995 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Acconci, Vito (2 of 2), 1995 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Boltanski, Christian - "Lost" (1 of 5), 1995 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Boltanski, Christian - "Lost" (2 of 5), 1995 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Boltanski, Christian - "Lost" (3 of 5), 1995 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Boltanski, Christian - "Lost" (4 of 5), 1995 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Boltanski, Christian - "Lost" (5 of 5), 1995 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - "What They Remember" Interviews, [1995] (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Abakanowicz, Magdalena - "Hand-Like Trees", 1996 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Brodsky, Alexander (1 of 2) - "Canal Street Subway Project", 1996 (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Brodsky, Alexander (2 of 2) - "Canal Street Subway Project", 1996 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Doyle, Chris - "Commutable", 1996 (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - Green, Gregory - "Gregnik Proto II", 1997 (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - Keith Haring on Park Avenue, 1 of 4, 1997 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - Keith Haring on Park Avenue, 2 of 4, 1997 (Box 46, Folder 21)
    - Keith Haring on Park Avenue, 3 of 4, 1997 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Keith Haring on Park Avenue, 4 of 4, 1997 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Kabakov, Ilya - "Monument to the Lost Glove", 1 of 2, 1997 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Kabakov, Ilya - "Monument to the Lost Glove", 2 of 2, 1997 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Kabakov, Ilya - "Permit", 1997 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Kruger, Barbara - "Bus", 1997 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Lipski, Donald - "The Yearling", 1997 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Saar, Alison and Betye - "Roots and Wings Garden", 1997 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - De Kooning, Willem, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Mosher, Kirstin - "Ball Park Traffic", 1998 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Rodin, Auguste at Rockefeller Center, 1 of 2, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Rodin, Auguste at Rockefeller Center, 2 of 2, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Smith, Tony - 1 of 3, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Smith, Tony - 2 of 3, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Smith, Tony - 3 of 3, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Whiteread, Rachel - "Water Tower" - 1 of 3, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Whiteread, Rachel - "Water Tower" - 2 of 3, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Whiteread, Rachel - "Water Tower" - 3 of 3, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - Whiteread, Rachel - Multiple, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Witz, Dan - "Sticks", 1998 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Acconci, Vito - "Rooms from Below: A Display System for Show Windows", 1999 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Baron, Ron - "Birds", 1999 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Gonzalez, Maria Elena - "Magic Carpet/Home", 1999 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Grennan, Simon and Christopher Sperandio - "The Invisible City", 1999 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Hill, Christine, 1999 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Jones, Kristin and Andrew Ginzel - "Metronome", 1 of 6, 1999 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Jones, Kristin and Andrew Ginzel - "Metronome", 2 of 6, 1999 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Jones, Kristin and Andrew Ginzel - "Metronome", 3 of 6, 1999 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Jones, Kristin and Andrew Ginzel - "Metronome", 4 of 6, 1999 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Jones, Kristin and Andrew Ginzel - "Metronome", 5 of 6, 1999 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Jones, Kristin and Andrew Ginzel - "Metronome", 6 of 6, 1999 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Manship, Paul Howard - "Manship at Rockefeller Center", 1999 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Matelli, Tony - "Distant Party", 1999 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Zittel, Andrea - 1 of 4, 1999 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Zittel, Andrea - 2 of 4, 1999 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Zittel, Andrea - 3 of 4, 1999 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Zittel, Andrea - 4 of 4, 1999 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - Beecroft, Vanessa - 1 of 2, 2000 (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - Beecroft, Vanessa - 2 of 2, 2000 (Box 48, Folder 20)
    - Creed, Martin, 2000 (Box 48, Folder 21)
    - Kabakov, Ilya & Emilia - "Palace of Projects" - 1 of 5, 2000 (Box 48, Folder 22)
    - Kabakov, Ilya & Emilia - "Palace of Projects" - 2 of 5, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Kabakov, Ilya & Emilia - "Palace of Projects" - 3 of 5, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Kabakov, Ilya & Emilia - "Palace of Projects" - 4 of 5, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Kabakov, Ilya & Emilia - "Palace of Projects" - 5 of 5, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Koons, Jeff - "Puppy" - 1 of 2, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Koons, Jeff - "Puppy" - 2 of 2, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Kruger, Barbara, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Long, Richard - 1 of 2, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Long, Richard - 2 of 2, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Oursler, Tony - 1 of 2, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Oursler, Tony - 2 of 2, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Rist, Pipilotti - "Open My Glade", 2000 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Taylor, Jocelyn - "The Story of Color", 2000 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Von Rydingsvard, Ursula - Bowl with Folds, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Weiner, Lawrence - "New York City Manhole Covers", 2000 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Westphalen, Olav - "E.S.U.S. Extremely Site Un-Specific Sculpture", 2000 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Bourgeois, Louise - 1 of 2, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Bourgeois, Louise - 2 of 2, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Cragg, Tony - "Turbo and Ferryman", 2001 (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - Fernández, Teresita - "Bamboo Cinema", 2001 (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - McCarthy, Paul - "The Box", 2001 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - McElheny, Josiah - "The Metal Party: Reconstructing a Party held in Dessau on February 9, 1929" - 1 of 2, 2001 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - McElheny, Josiah - "The Metal Party: Reconstructing a Party held in Dessau on February 9, 1929" - 2 of 2, 2001 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Pfeiffer, Paul - "Orpheus Descending", 2001 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Ramirez Jonas, Paul - "Every Day", 2001 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Rawanchaikul, Navin - "I Love Taxi" - 1 of 3, 2001 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Rawanchaikul, Navin - "I Love Taxi" - 2 of 3, 2001 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Rawanchaikul, Navin - "I Love Taxi" - 3 of 3, 2001 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Rehberger, Tobias - 1 of 3, 2001 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Rehberger, Tobias - 2 of 3, 2001 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Rehberger, Tobias - 3 of 3, 2001 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Alÿs, Francis - "The Modern Procession" - 1 of 2, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Alÿs, Francis - "The Modern Procession" - 2 of 2, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Dalziel + Scullion - "Voyager", 2002 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Dion, Mark - "Urban Wildlife Observation", 2002 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Edmier, Keith - "Emil Dobbelstein and Henry J. Drope, 1944", 2002 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Freeman, Jonah - Sixteen Scenarios, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Freeman, Jonah & Mack, Anissa, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - Graham, Dan - Bisected Triangle, Interior Curve, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Mack, Anissa - Pies for a Passerby, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - Muniz, Vik - CandyBAM, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 21)
    - Munoz, Juan - "Conversation Piece" - 1 of 2, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 22)
    - Munoz, Juan - "Conversation Piece" - 2 of 2, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 23)
    - Paik, Nam June - "Transmission", 2002 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Paik, Nam June - "Transmission" - Press/ Anne Wehr, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Paine, Roxy - "Bluff", 2002 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Smith, Kiki - "Sirens and Harpies", 2002 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Sooja, Kim - "Deductive Object", 2002 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Tolle, Brian - "Waylay", 2002 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Delvoye, Wim - "Gothic Works", 2003 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Delvoye, Wim - "Caterpillar" & "Chantier", 2003 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Handforth, Mark - "Lamppost", 2003 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Mori, Mariko - "Wave UFO" - Press, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Mori, Mariko - "Wave UFO" - Contracts, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Mori, Mariko - "Wave UFO" - Project plan, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Mori, Mariko - "Wave UFO" - Installation, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Mori, Mariko - "Wave UFO" - Budget, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Mori, Mariko - "Wave UFO" - Intern questionnaire, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Mori, Mariko - "Wave UFO" - Press - Anne Wehr 1 of 2, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Mori, Mariko - "Wave UFO" - Press - Anne Wehr 2 of 2, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Murakami, Takashi - "Reversed Double Helix" - 1 of 6, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Murakami, Takashi - "Reversed Double Helix" - 2 of 6, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Murakami, Takashi - "Reversed Double Helix" - 3 of 6, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - Murakami, Takashi - "Reversed Double Helix" - 4 of 6, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - Murakami, Takashi - "Reversed Double Helix" - 5 of 6, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - Murakami, Takashi - "Reversed Double Helix" - 6 of 6, 2003 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Segal, George - "Street Crossing", 2003 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Williams, Clara - "The Price (Giving in Gets You Nowhere)", 2003 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Altmejd, David - "Untitled (Swallow)" and "Untitled (Bluejay)", 2004 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - assume vivid astro focus, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Borofsky, Jonathan - 1 of 3, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Borofsky, Jonathan - 2 of 3, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Borofsky, Jonathan - 3 of 3, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Cardiff, Janet - "Her Long Black Hair" - 1 of 6, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Cardiff, Janet - "Her Long Black Hair" - 2 of 6, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Cardiff, Janet - "Her Long Black Hair" - 3 of 6, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Cardiff, Janet - "Her Long Black Hair" - 4 of 6, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Cardiff, Janet - "Her Long Black Hair" - 5 of 6, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Cardiff, Janet - "Her Long Black Hair" - 6 of 7, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Cardiff, Janet - "Her Long Black Hair" - 7 of 7, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Craft, Liz - "The Spare", 2004 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Haring, Keith, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - Kereszi, Lisa & Moore, Andrew - "Governor's Island" - 1 of 2, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - Kereszi, Lisa & Moore, Andrew - "Governor's Island" - 2 of 2, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Kusama, Yayoi - "Narcissus Garden", 2004 (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - McCarthy, Paul - "Daddies Bighead", 2004 (Box 52, Folder 21)
    - McCollum, Allan - "Perfect Vehicles", 2004 (Box 52, Folder 22)
    - Muller, Dave - "Themeless (A Carnival of Sorts)", 2004 (Box 52, Folder 23)
    - Opie, Julian - "Animals, Buildings, Cars, and People" - 1 of 5, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 24)
    - Opie, Julian - "Animals, Buildings, Cars, and People" - 2 of 5, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 25)
    - Opie, Julian - "Animals, Buildings, Cars, and People" - 3 of 5, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 26)
    - Opie, Julian - "Animals, Buildings, Cars, and People" - 4 of 5, 2004 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Opie, Julian - "Animals, Buildings, Cars, and People" - 5 of 5, 2004 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - West, Franz - 1 of 3, 2004 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - West, Franz - 2 of 3, 2004 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - West, Franz - 3 of 3, 2004 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Westphalen, Olav - "The Weight of Dead Prey", 2004 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Deacon, Richard - "Masters of the Universe": Screen Version, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Deacon, Richard - "Masters of the Universe": Screen Version - 2 of 2, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Diaz, Alejandro - "A Can For All Seasons", 2005 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Huyghe, Pierre - "A Journey That Wasn't" - 1 of 5, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Huyghe, Pierre - "A Journey That Wasn't" - 2 of 5, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Huyghe, Pierre - "A Journey That Wasn't" - 3 of 5, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Huyghe, Pierre - "A Journey That Wasn't" - 4 of 5, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Huyghe, Pierre - "A Journey That Wasn't" - 5 of 5, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Kentridge, William - "9 Drawings for Projection" - 1 of 3, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Kentridge, William - "9 Drawings for Projection" - 2 of 3, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Kentridge, William - "9 Drawings for Projection" - 3 of 3, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Murakami, Takashi - "Cool Japan", 2005 (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Murakami, Takashi - "Little Boy" - 1 of 9, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - Murakami, Takashi - "Little Boy" - 2 of 9, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - Murakami, Takashi - "Little Boy" - 3 of 9, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - Murakami, Takashi - "Little Boy" - 4 of 9, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 22)
    - Murakami, Takashi - "Little Boy" - 5 of 9, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 23)
    - Murakami, Takashi - "Little Boy" - 6 of 9, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 24)
    - Murakami, Takashi - "Little Boy" - 7 of 9, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Murakami, Takashi - "Little Boy" - 8 of 9, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Murakami, Takashi - "Little Boy" - 9 of 9, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Smith, Allison - "The Muster" - 1 of 4, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Smith, Allison - "The Muster" - 2 of 4, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Smith, Allison - "The Muster" - 3 of 4, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Smith, Allison - "The Muster" - 4 of 4, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Smith, Allison - "The Muster" - Images - 1 of 2, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Smith, Allison - "The Muster" - Images - 2 of 2, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Robert Therrien - "Table and Six Chairs", 2005 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Witenstein, Ivan - "Uncle John's Band" - 1 of 2, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Witenstein, Ivan - "Uncle John's Band" - 2 of 2, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Calder, Alexander - "Alexander Calder in New York" - 1 of 3, 2006 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Calder, Alexander - "Alexander Calder in New York" - 2 of 3, 2006 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Calder, Alexander - "Alexander Calder in New York" - 3 of 3, 2006 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Kapoor, Anish - "Sky Mirror" - 1 of 2, 2006 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Kapoor, Anish - "Sky Mirror" - 2 of 2, 2006 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Katchadourian, Nina - "Office Semaphore", 2006 (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Larner, Liz - 1 of 3, 2006 (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Larner, Liz - 2 of 3, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - Larner, Liz - 3 of 3, 2005 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Morris, Sarah - Robert Towne - 1 of 3, 2006 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Morris, Sarah - Robert Towne - 2 of 3, 2006 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Morris, Sarah - Robert Towne - 3 of 3, 2006 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Rubins, Nancy - "Big Pleasure Point" - 1 of 7, 2006 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Rubins, Nancy - "Big Pleasure Point" - 2 of 7, 2006 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Rubins, Nancy - "Big Pleasure Point" - 3 of 7, 2006 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Rubins, Nancy - "Big Pleasure Point" - 4 of 7, 2006 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Rubins, Nancy - "Big Pleasure Point" - 5 of 7, 2006 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Rubins, Nancy - "Big Pleasure Point" - 6 of 7, 2006 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Rubins, Nancy - "Big Pleasure Point" - 7 of 7, 2006 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Sze, Sarah - "Corner Plot", 2006 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Beth Campbell - Potential Store Fronts - 1 of 2, 2007 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Beth Campbell - Potential Store Fronts - 2 of 2, 2007 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Creed, Martin - "Variety Store" - 1 of 7, 2007 (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Creed, Martin - "Variety Store" - 2 of 7, 2007 (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - Creed, Martin - "Variety Store" - 3 of 7, 2007 (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - Creed, Martin - "Variety Store" - 4 of 7, 2007 (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - Creed, Martin - "Variety Store" - 5 of 7, 2007 (Box 55, Folder 19)
    - Creed, Martin - "Variety Store" - 6 of 7, 2007 (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - Creed, Martin - "Variety Store" - 7 of 7, 2007 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Friedman, Dara, 2007 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Lucas, Sarah - 1 of 2, 2007 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Lucas, Sarah - 2 of 3, 2007 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Lucas, Sarah - 3 of 3, 2007 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Ortega, Damien - 1 of 2, 2007 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Ortega, Damien - 2 of 2, 2007 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Graham, Rodney - "The Rodney Graham Band" - 1 of 3, 2008 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Graham, Rodney - "The Rodney Graham Band" - 2 of 3, 2008 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Graham, Rodney - "The Rodney Graham Band" - 3 of 3, 2008 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Jankowski, Christian, 2008 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Melee, Robert - "It Sitting, It standing, It Up, Her Leaving", 2008 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Yamada, James - "Our Starry Night" - 1 of 4, 2009 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Yamada, James - "Our Starry Night" - 2 of 4, 2009 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Yamada, James - "Our Starry Night" - 3 of 4, 2009 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Yamada, James - "Our Starry Night" - 4 of 4, 2009 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Farris, Julie and Wayland-Smith, Sarah - "A Clearing in the Streets" - 1 of 2, 2009 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Farris, Julie and Wayland-Smith, Sarah - "A Clearing in the Streets" - 1 of 2, 2009 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Subseries VI.B: In the Public Realm
    Arranged chronologically, this series documents Public Art Fund's In The Public Realm program, initiated by director Tom Eccles in 1995 to support public art projects by New York-based emerging artists. Materials include documentation of realized projects, as well as proposals from In the Public Realm finalists.
    - Beth B. - "A Day of Hope", 1992 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - In the Public Realm 1996 - 1 of 2 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - In the Public Realm 1996 - 2 of 2 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Adkins, Terry - "In the Public Realm" Proposal, [1997] (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - In the Public Realm 1997 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - In the Public Realm 1998 - 1 of 2 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - In the Public Realm 1998 - 2 of 2, 1996 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - In the Public Realm 1999 - 1 of 2 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - In the Public Realm 1999 - 2 of 2 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - deMar, Rob - "Metropolitan Fungi" - Art in the Public Realm, 1999 (Box 57, Folder 15)